

#### CONTACT

9865657440

khadka.sakar10@gmail.c

Kailali Nepal

in sacarkhadka

ig\_sacar

#### **EDUCATION**

# Diploma In Computer Engineering

Nepalgunj Technical College / Nepalgunj / July, 2019 - Present

#### **Computer Operator**

Alpine Technical College / Dhangadhi / September, 2017 -December, 2018

I Completed my computer operator study from Alpine Technical College

#### **SKILLS**

- Game Development Expert
- Graphic Designing Experienced
- Video Editing Experienced

#### **LANGUAGE**

# Sakar Khadka

#### About Me

I am a highly skilled and experienced game developer with a passion for creating engaging and immersive gaming experiences. I have 2 years of experience in the game development industry, and have worked on a variety of projects. Also have experience in computer operator with a strong background in operating and maintaining computer systems and networks.

#### **AWARDS**

#### Level 2 Award

Fiverr / 2021 / United State

Received a Level 2 Award after completing the Milestone Fiverr Promote me as a Level 2 Seller

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### IT Project Manager

Kushmi Tech Pvt.Ltd / Tikapur / June, 2019 - Present

Managed a team of 10+ IT Experts From all over the world

Created a School Management System For the better

Improvement

#### **Freelancer Game Developer**

Fiverr / United State / July, 2021 - Present

Work as a professional Indie Game Developer on Fiverr as a Freelancer. The Major Job was to make an Android, IOS & PC Games

#### **Teaching**

Name Technical College / Nepalgunj / September, 2022 - Present Work as a IT teacher at Name Technical College.

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Built a School Management System**

I was a Project Manager while creating this system. We created this Software to manage the overall activities of School In a Digital Manner.

https://www.trueemis.com

## **Build Multiple 2D & 3D Android Games**

I had created multiple games on Unity Engine as a Freelancer. To fulfill the requirements of my clients

#### **Built A Multiplayer PC Game**

I had created an NFT Based Multiplayer Game as per the client requirement

